[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which type of tax is taken directly out of your paycheck??",
        "a": "What kind of grades you earn.",
        "b": "Whether or not you pay your bills on time (your credit history).",
        "c": "Your intended date of graduation.",
        "d": "All of the above",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "Your intended date of graduation.",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which of the following is a risk to consider when investing?",
        "a": "You could lose all of your money",
        "b": "Inflation",
        "c": "Your money is not liquid",
        "d": "All of the above",
        "correct": "b",
        "answer": "Inflation",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In terms of size what position does the Indian economy occupy in the world?",
        "a": "10th",
        "b": "12th",
        "c": "7th",
        "d": "9th",
        "correct": "b",
        "answer": "12th",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which industry provides the largest employment in India?",
        "a": "Orenge",
        "b": "Textiles",
        "c": "Iron and steel",
        "d": "Jute",
        "correct": "b",
        "answer": "Textiles",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has launched which app?",
        "a": "Pay Commission Mobile App",
        "b": "National Budget App",
        "c": "Union Budget Mobile App",
        "d": "Budget App",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "Union Budget Mobile App",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The State Bank of India allocated how much amount towards the fight against Covid 19?",
        "a": "Rs.70 cr",
        "b": "Rs.92 cr",
        "c": "Rs.71 cr",
        "d": "Rs.60 cr",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "Rs.71 cr",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which of the following organisation has introduced the flagship initiative Liberalised MSME AEO Package scheme?",
        "a": "CBIC",
        "b": "ONGC",
        "c": "Niti Aayog",
        "d": "Ministry of Planning",
        "correct": "a",
        "answer": "CBIC",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Government aims to gradually increase the public health expenditure to what percent of Gross Domestic Product by 2025?",
        "a": "0.015",
        "b": "3.5%",
        "c": "4.5%",
        "d": "2.5%",
        "correct": "d",
        "answer": "2.5%",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "favourite language?",
        "a": "python",
        "b": "C++",
        "c": "java",
        "d": "js",
        "correct": "d",
        "answer": "js",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Who has been appointed as the 1st chairman of the International Financial Services Centre Authority for a 3 years term?",
        "a": "Injeti Srinivas",
        "b": "Sumanta Chaudhury",
        "c": "Anant Narayan Nanda",
        "d": "Arun Goel",
        "correct": "a",
        "answer": "Injeti Srinivas",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Who is the current US president",
        "a": "Obama",
        "b": "Bush",
        "c": "Biden",
        "d": "Trumph",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "Biden",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Which of thw following is a Tech Stack",
        "a": "MEAN",
        "b": "MERN",
        "c": "MYIO",
        "d": "None of the above",
        "correct": "b",
        "answer": "MERN",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "PM of india",
        "a": "Narendra modi",
        "b": "sd",
        "c": "sfd",
        "d": "sfd",
        "correct": "a",
        "answer": "Narendra modi",
        "explanation": "Explanation"
    }
]